# Matthew Macklin - Full Stack Developer / Python / Javascript

MATTHEWTHOMASMACKLIN@GMAIL.COM + 44 7716 002 309 WWW.FRACTAL-SWIFT.COM GITHUB.COM/FRACTALSWIFT

#### **PROFILE**

I work with Python and Javascript. I have extensive experience consuming REST api with both languages, and building them in Node and Flask. I have built mobile applications in React Native as well as PWAs with Gatsby. I love people and I love solving problems, and I am interested in roles at companies with a modern tech stack and a skilled, motivated team that I can join and push myself. - please don't hesitate to get in contact with any questions.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python: Pandas, Numpy, Django, Pytest, OOP, XGboost (machine learning)

JavaScript: ReactJS, React Native, Redux, Node.js, Express, JSON

Others: Git, HTML/CSS, PostgreSQL REST API, JSON, Docker, XGboost, Smart Contracts (Solidity), Linux

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### FREELANCE DEVELOPER FOR ALGORITHMIC TRADERS 2017 - PRESENT

- Built and run tools for collecting and analysing exchange data via REST API with Python
- Build and run trading robots via REST API / Websocket
- Deployment on Digital Ocean

### FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER, 2010- 2014

- Built and maintained e-commerce and other websites using Wordpress/Woo-commerce, React, Gatsby and Shopify.

### PROJECT MANAGER DEVON DANCE PROJECT 2014 - 2017

Not a software role, just including for completeness. I designed, delivered and evaluated projects funded with over £60,000 of Arts Council England grants and lead a team of 4 people. This role involved building and managing relationships with various stakeholders and mentoring younger colleagues. I maintained a casual practice of software skills during this time but it was not my main focus.

## SIDE PROJECTS

## DEVON WRESTLING MATCH APP

- Special timer for Devon Wrestling rule set in React JS / React Native

### ROADVIZ

- App using Chart.js and DeckGL via React to visualise uk traffic data. Uses Express on the backend.

# CRYPTOZAP

-Django web app for checking liquidity at various cryptocurrency exchanges via REST API

### **EDUCATION**

UNIVERSITY OF EXETER — MA ENGLISH LITERATURE: CRITICISM AND THEORY (DISTINCTION) 2010 UNIVERSITY OF EXETER — BA ENGLISH LITERATURE (FIRST CLASS) 2008